I want to be your girlfriend more. I want you to like me more.
I love you so much when I look at you
I'll show you that it's not enough just to look at me
I'll have the courage to tell you
Spells are love's best friend
I'll tell you how much I love you if you look at me
Ah, Hana-san, it's 8:00
Oh, Shin-chan's furious.
That's great
Oh, wait a minute
Range change
Ah, lately
If I do this, you won't be able to see if I scoot
One corner.
Yes, sir.
Don't go back.
You're on your way.
Me?
Oh, here we go.
Three, two, one.
You want to do it from here?
Are you meeting anyone tonight after this?
Would you like to go out with me?
I knew it. I can't watch this.
I'm so sorry.
Who have I been seeing?
Who do you think? Who do you think?
Who do you think?
I've been...
Lele-le-le-le-le-le-le-le-le-le-le-le-le-le-le-le-le-le-le-le-le-le-le-le-le-le-le-le.
Sir, I just wanted to have a chat with a guy who was passing by.
Even after the rain, it's still a banana chat party.
Let's go!
Ame flash chatting even during the rain shooting!
Ameshabee for short!
Sorry.
Good evening to all of you who are watching our official YouTube Live Ameflash channel.
Good evening.
We are AmeFlash.
And so, the name calling for the title call this time
This time, we have a board member, Ojisan-san, who is just passing by.
This time, we chose a board member, an uncle who is passing by.
Something like, that One More Time was released last week, right, the music video?
That's right, six years ago, I was walking around all summer with Momokuro-san.
I was able to see the kids who were hand-selling 3B Junior's goods while walking around Momokuro's summer six years ago, grow up.
I'm so moved, the chosen four.
Go AmeFlash. I'll be rooting for you. Let's make it to Fukuoka again.
Thank you for your kind comments.
Thank you so much.
I didn't know it was like this. I've come this far.
I've grown up so far.
Only the inside hasn't changed.
If it came as it is, it would be a big problem.
It's interesting even if it's changed.
Like the silly feeling.
The title call, the part about how I've always wanted to talk to ____.
I'm going to pick one of the people who tweeted their thoughts on the candy chat.
I will call that person's name.
Please.
I would appreciate it if you could tweet your thoughts on the show with the hashtag Amezaibo.
Thank you in advance.
Spacha is here as soon as possible.
Thank you even from Mr. Toi to everyone who is more excited than usual.
Yae Katsura-san is looking forward to Yakiniku King's Japan Fair starting on June 21.
What is that?
I'm sorry. I'll have a look at the menu now.
Let me see.
Let me guess. Matcha.
I want matcha.
So that's what it is.
That's what it was last time, right? It was a Korean fair, right?
It was a Korean fair last time, wasn't it?
I wonder.
I wanted to go to the Korea Fair one more time.
It's Japan, right? Japan, right?
What is it?
Give it to me safely.
Safe.
Wow. This is bad.
I wanna see.
What do you think it is?
Japan Fest, right?
So now we're talking about bracken cakes and unagi (eel)?
Unagi?
What?
Ah.
Or those Japanese sweets and dumplings.
That's for sure.
That's what I meant.
Mini taiyaki.
The strongest baked goods.
Wow, yummy.
Magazine soup takoyaki.
Takoyaki?
I see.
Inaniwa style? What is this? Inate-style?
Inaniwa style, I guess.
Inaniwa-style udon.
Udon.
And potato korori. Mentaiko potato korori.
Oh, man. I definitely want to eat it.Oh no. I definitely want to eat it.
And the Ishiyaki Eel Rice.
I'm going to put eel in it.
Look, look, look.
Isn't this Ishiyaki bad?
Grilled shabu kalbi. Yuck!
Kalbi?
I want some.
Kalbi.
This is bad.
Can I go now?
Sure.
I want to go!
It says June 21.
How many days is today?
Nineteen days.
Wow.
I want to go.
Thank you. For telling me.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Kazu-kun.
The four of you, Omeifushimasen. Especially Aira-chan.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
No, but please make sure that everyone gets well equally.
I don't want only Aira to get well.
You know, the engine will start too much.
Even the tabre is here for Aira.
Always.
Always be here.
That's right.
Thank you very much.
Well, well, if it's a usual American chat, it's normal to start a farce here, or something,
But tonight we don't have time for that. Gentlemen.
What do you think?
I have something to tell you.
Yes, that's right.
Biosign sold out!
Yay!
We did great!
Thank you so much.
I'm also wearing my superco sold out spacha.
Only the Ameflas team is excited.
No, but if we can get the Ameflas team excited, that's all that matters.
YTXZ Shipponokimochi, congrats on the sold out.
It's getting hotter. Eat and drink something cool and stay active.
One More Time very good!
Thank you very much.
I will have you add your feelings.
That's right.
Um, a minute or two,
I'm really glad.
Glad?
I'm very happy.
Don't forget to come.
We talked a lot with the staff about how we could sell out the show,
We talked a lot with the staff about how we could sell out the show and how many tickets we could get,
Then, we would put this out at this stage and see if we could get a few more people to show up,
We were planning a lot of things, right?
We were thinking about how we could sell tickets to the staff,
At the next stage,
Next step,
Next step... Next step..,
At the next stage
Next step,
There was the next stage, wasn't there?
You had a ticket before you got to the stage where you said, "If I do this, there will be a little more to come,
Sold out,
About a month ago.
I'm really happy.
Isn't that a first?
First time?
It's a first. Less than a month ago,
Sold out, both copies.
I'm so happy.
I'm happy.
Even though it's bigger than the last show,
I know, right?
Thank you very much. Really.
Thank you very much.
So, I have a surprise for you all today.
What a surprise that Eiko Festival, isn't it?
The visual,
Visual,
I would like to show you,
I would like to show you.
There are two versions, one part and the other part.
Let's start with the first part.
Here is the first part.
Boom!
Power!Power!
It's summer.
It's summery.
Sorry.
Is this the second part?
Is that two parts?
I thought you said this was part two.
Okay, let's start with part two.
Didn't you say one part earlier?
You said one part.
Well, okay.
Okay, I'll show you.
One part.
Okay, this is part two.
This is part one.
There you go.
It's the exact opposite.
I wonder.
One part is monochrome.
The second part is a cute pop with a little bit of pinkish color.
Oh, it's cool.
It's a little bit printed.
It might be hard to tell.
Four, six, five, six.
Stegill!
Summer.
Cute.
You were a little late with last week's delivery, weren't you?
Yes, we were.
We couldn't start on time.
You were shooting from a different location than usual, right?
I was shooting this.
Wow.
So it was freshly shot?
Yes, that's right.
Oh, the glowing fan. That's right.
It's the same as the real glowing fan that you will receive.
Yes.
Oh, that's right. Let's put A-chan in there too.
Hey. It glows blue, right?
Right?
It's like a baiser personality.
If it glows.
I want this too, but I'm not sure if it'll be in the data... so I hope you're looking forward to it in the data too.
I know it's not much, but it's rare to see candy this cute.
Isn't it cute? I always have Moeka in a ponytail and Ira in a ponytail, but it's the opposite and it's cute.
I also have twin-tail hair, a little different from usual, and a nose that's different too.
I like it... it's great... it's like the shape of her mouth... You're right, I don't often have a mouth like this.
Chick consciousness? I was thinking of a chick in my yellow outfit. I'm not funny, I'm the same.
I'm sorry... don't make fun of Asha... but maybe next time you can do her hair like this...
I'll wear it as a daisy.
I'll do a decent hairpiece. This one?
No, no, no. You can wear it.
I'm sorry, can we get a little closer to Ira?
A little closer to Ira?
That's great. You sure you don't want to be too close?
No, I'm just happy to be in nerd company.
You're happy? I kind of hate it when I'm the one who's happy.
I'm happy.
It's okay, it's okay.
So, the new visuals have been released,
I'm sure you're all looking forward to it,
I hope you are all looking forward to the two parts of the show, which will be really different,
The tickets are sold out, so if you were not able to buy a ticket, you can still buy one at the door,
If you couldn't buy a ticket, there are still a lot of places to go, such as Lilywei.
Please come and join us there as well.
Please come to the last day of the event.
There are no tickets for this one, so you can come no matter how big the capacity is.
There is no upper limit.
Even 50,000 people can come.
And we're wearing new costumes, you know.
Sober.
Sober new costumes.
That's right. Sober. Slippery.
It has a new costume.
New costumes, or rather, bio-sign costumes.
Flower Can yellow.
Ira pink.
Moe-face orange.
Yuzu green.
What a rarity.
They're all unusual, aren't they?
I don't wear pink.
Surprising, isn't it?
All I see is Isla in pink.
That's because she's red.
Yeah, there's a lot of pink.
There's a lot of pink.
That's for sure.
They're all unusual and pretty.
Look forward to it.
Please do.
I really appreciate all the publicity and the invitation of my friends to come to the event,
I would like to thank all of you for your support and for inviting your friends,
We will do our best not to let you down,
Let's enjoy the concert together.
Please enjoy the show with us.
I hope you will enjoy the concert with us.
I'll do my best not to let you down.Hey.
You too, Amrider.
Let's have fun.
Yes, I will.
So, the biosigning is already here.
I will do my best to give you the best live show ever.
So, once again, I would like to thank each one of you and express my determination for the live show.
Let's do it.
Yes, I'll do it.
Okay, Yuzu.
Okay, Yuzu. First of all, thank you very much for the ticket soul art.
YuzuYou might say, "That's not the point,
But I'm very much interested in the soul art of the ticket,
I think Amefurashi is such a good group,
I was really frustrated because I wondered why we couldn't make soul art for every ticket, even though Ameflasi is such a good group,
I wanted more people to see our music,
I was frustrated because I wanted more people to see the show, and of course I was happy to see soul art on the day of the show,
I have been aiming to make soul art even before the show, not just on the day of the show, of course,
I'm very happy that both parts of the show came true,
I'm very happy that both parts of the concert came true, and I'm also very happy that the releases I'm doing now were not in vain,
I am very happy about that,
I'm very happy about the excitement that everyone is looking forward to now,
We will do our best to make the excitement that everyone is looking forward to now enjoyable so that they don't feel disappointed with us,
We will do our best in our lessons so that you will not feel disappointed,
So if you would like to join us, please listen to the various coffees and other songs with excitement,
I hope you will all enjoy listening to the various coffee songs and other music, and learn more and more in preparation for the show.
I hope you will enjoy it with us.
Please do.
I'll go now.
I'm really glad that everyone was able to come out of the room.
Thank you very much.
I really don't think that sold-out is everything,
Of course I'm happy that we sold out,
But I was really happy that so many fans came to see the show,
That's how fans spread the word,
I think we were able to take another step forward thanks to the support of all the fans who spread the word,
I think we were able to fill this venue to capacity,
Now that we were able to fill this venue, I think we will be able to perform on a bigger stage next time,
I hope to be able to show you a more matured Amefurashi again,
We will continue to work hard in the lessons today and in the future,
I hope everyone is looking forward to the Bayou Festival.
I hope you are all looking forward to the Bayou Festival,
I hope you are all looking forward to the Bayou Festival.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for the soul dough.
I can't move on to the next step if I don't do the Soul Doubt,
I can't go to the next stage unless I do the Soul Doubt,
I'm really happy about this,
I had a feeling that we would sell out in a minute or two,
But the fans helped us, the members, the staff, and others,
I'm really happy that we were able to do this with the help of the fans, the members, the staff, and everyone's help in promoting the event, and that we were able to do this,
I'm really looking forward to seeing the venue packed with people, and I'm really excited about it,
I'm really looking forward to seeing a full house, and I'm really excited about rehearsals and performing some of the new coffee songs that we haven't performed yet,
I hope everyone has a great time,
I hope everyone will have a great time, and I can't wait to go to the next one-man show,
I want to give you a great live performance so that you will want to go to the next one-man show again,
I want to do my best to make you love Amefurakko even more,
I hope you all enjoy Amefura's live performance on July 9!
Don't forget to come to our live show and look forward to it!
Thank you so much!
Thank you all so much for your support.
I'm sure you all had a great time at the Soul Doubt before we went out,
I was wondering if you would like to do the Soul Doubt? I was really happy and I was really happy too.
Everyone was really happy, and I was really happy too,
I'm also very happy for those who came to the event for the first time at the re-leave,
Or people who saw us on TikTok,
I've received DMs from people who applied with a light heart and wondered if it would be OK,
We are not just for those people,
We want to do our best to make this a great show for those who come,
I think there are people who have applied for the show with various thoughts and feelings.
I think there are people who have applied for the show with various thoughts and feelings,
I think that there are people who are feeling down and want to go to the Ameerah City concert,
There are also those who simply want to have fun,
We want to entertain them as much as we can,
We hope you will listen to the music, but even if you don't understand it, we will entertain you,
So please don't worry, you can enjoy the show even if you don't know the music,
So please feel free to come to our concerts.
I hope you all will come to the concert with peace of mind.
I hope you all enjoy the show.
Let's have fun.
Spa-chan is here too, so I'll read it.
Congratulations on selling out both parts of the biosai from Chyu-san.
A-chan's, huh?
A-chan is here.
What about us? I'm already looking forward to it.
She's coming out.
Thank you very much.
Yusuke, congratulations on selling out BioSai.
I'm looking forward to your best performance.
Thank you very much.
Next, congratulations to Ogubi-san for selling out.
BioSci will give you the best performance and the best support.
Thank you very much.
That's all.
Let's have fun.
Yes, I know.
It's like, everyone is coming here today saying they are serious.
We always said we were serious, didn't we?
Today, I don't want to be serious or anything, but I want to thank you for this spiritedness,I'm not being serious or anything today, but this spirited thank you,
No, thank you, seriously.
It's bad when I do it.
It's true.
The truth is, I'm surprisingly serious.
I'm going to be serious today.
You have to be serious.
I'm not serious.
I just want to be tough here.
I don't know what I'll look like if I say, "That's right," and then come in.
One more thing.
If you were serious, you would have gone to school at the school accountant's office.
I think it's fine to be serious.
We are serious, aren't we? We are.
I think we are serious just because we graduated from school.
I'm here at Bircher.
I'd like to read it.
Coffee. Congratulations on the toast.
And I've been enjoying every day since I met Ameflash,
I am sure that I will make my dream of becoming a barbecue chef come true.
I know you have a lot of hard work ahead of you, but I wish you all the best.
Thank you very much.
I'm going to go eat there.
Please make it cheap.
You're trying to spend too much.
Yakiniku King is surprisingly cheap.
All-you-can-eat.
It's not Yakiniku King.
He's not the owner of Yakiniku King.
He wants to run his own butcher shop.
I thought he was a great guy.
He's not the owner of Yakiniku King, is he?
I'm not aiming for that.
I'm not aiming for that. I'll be surprised if someone says, "Are you the manager of Yakiniku King?
That's amazing. It's very hard to smoke.
Thank you very much.
We've been here for two minutes and our hearts are burning with enthusiasm.
I have a proposal for the eldest here to show that the feeling is real,
What is it?
May I?
Yes, I have a proposal.
You see the character "moe" in Moeka Suzuki's name?
How about changing it to the character for "combustion"? How about changing it to "burning"?
Why?
Here it is.
Then!
Moeka.
Oh, I see.
What do you think, Mr. Suzuki?
Why?
I think it's really good.
I think it's really good, in my opinion.
I can feel Moka Moka's spirit in "Burning Flowers".
But..,
I want to change the name to this.
No, how about changing the name to "Moka" (花) and "Hana" (花) to "Fire" (火)?
No, it's different.
It's great.
But I can really feel the burning feeling,
But, you know, if you only use the first name, it's not so good, so I'm going to bring back "Suzuki" as well.
There are a lot of Suzuki shamisen players, right?
There are a lot of Suzuki shamisen players.
There are a lot of people named Suzuki, so I'll call them Gondawara.
Why Gondawara?
Gondawara, how about Moeka?
It's good, it's good.
Oh, I see.
Gon-chan.
Oh, sure.
It's really nice to have a gap between the two.
Gon-chan.
Gondawara, Moeka, it's starting to look like that now, isn't it?
Why not?
Why not Gon-chan?
Gon-chan.
Not Gon-chan!
Moeka's not Gon-chan!
Hey, idiot!
You said yourself that you didn't want to waste time with farce today.
Yeah.
And yet, you keep on bringing in farce like it's on a script.
Ignore this damn script!
Think for yourself and make your own MC!
Why are you doing this!
That's right.
And Yuzu!
You are the worst!
Burning fire?
What's that!
You just exposed everything that you can't say here and now you've set it ablaze?
Love at the end!
I don't know if I got buzz or what,
I don't know if it's buzz or what, but I'm filling all the cute slots in the candy flap!
You're supposed to be silly and emotional!
Come on, you're in the cute category!
Yes, Gon-chan.Yes, Gon-chan.
That ain't Gong-chan!
You're totally licking it.
You have no respect for the oldest, do you?
Gon-chan.
That's enough!
Moeka is transferring to the Chotokimeki Advertising Department!
That's no good!
It's vibes!
Let's go for it!
Let's work together!
Some people are gonna come!
From the coolest type of people, all of a sudden!
I think it's better to be responsible until the end.
If we go for the cool type, that's not the way to go!
What will happen? It's different again!
That's not right, is it?
Okay! I'll go! I'll transfer to you, Tokishimi-chan!
Shall we go with me and Kishimi-chan here then?
I have no choice, I'll transfer.
Well then, that's enough.
I, the oldest, will drink my tears and transfer.
Go ahead.
Hey! I'm not going to Tokishimi-chan!
It's a candy flash for the four of us!
It doesn't matter if I put on any one of you!
Moeka!
Gong-chan!
Gon-chan!
Why?
We got caught in the middle of an accident.
Yes, sir! That's why.
Did you enjoy Moeka's sharp game tonight, which is in demand by a very few people?
What do you think?
Did I seem to have slipped?
It's not what I expected.
Which one was the finished product?
I didn't know the right answer.
I didn't know.
Well, that's not the point.
You were looking for the hashtag "Moeichi got angry".
It was solicited without my permission.
It was a question that I wanted you to listen to with all your heart.
There was.
Was there?
Yes, there was. Yes, there was.
Why is Aiji choosing it? That's strange, isn't it?
I was responsible for recruiting them.
There were 4 applications.
Four?
Four.
Nurse!
Thank you very much.
I don't know if that's a lot.
I will answer them politely.
I will read one of them.
Thank you very much. Really.
It is from Shi-chan.
Dad! Don't leave only one pot of tea left! Make tea when it gets low!
Moe! Please get angry instead.
It's just that you leave a little bit.
It's very common.
When her father did it, Shi-chan got angry.
It's a common thing, isn't it? They don't want to do it, don't want to throw it away, don't want to change it, so they leave the last little bit.
This is a common thing among Japanese people.
It's a common thing for fathers.
Everyone does it.
Shin-chan is not here!
Shin-chan is missing!
What should I do with this?
Shinpapa!
I want you to get angry instead
Shin-pa!
Oh!
Don't leave a little.
Mayaka, go to your room.
I've got a couple of bottles of water in my room.
My mom gets mad at me a lot.
Don't do that.
That's all. I'm weak. What should I do next time?
Throw it away. Don't throw it away. Throw it away again.
Don't throw it away, but rebuild it.
Do it yourself.
I'm looking for it, I'm looking for it, I'm looking for it.
Don't use people.
See papa, see papa.
Do you understand? Do you understand?
Reflect on it. Reflect on it.
Are you really doing it? Are you really doing it?
Are you really doing it?
You can't see justice.
You can still apologize.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Can I ask you to think for yourself?
I mean, it's just the way it is.Because it's just the way it is.
I'm out of love
I'm losing my love for you
I can't stand it, I can't stand it
I'm losing love even more!
Oh, my God! Calm down!
Calm down.
Boo-boo! What is this?
What's this? Oh, no! Oh, no!
I can't believe she's going in for a broadcast accident... she's the type to start this year.
I'm not going to ask you to do it...
You're asking me to do that?
You're the one making me angry, so make yourself angry.
So, are you ready for this skit, Shaban, or are we done?
I'm done with this skit, Shaban...
Yuzu-chan will be performing at the Seeker's Parlap tomorrow!
Tickets are sold out immediately!
This week, I'll be performing with Rumpan, and we'll have a special benefit for a photo with Rumpan.
I'm hoping to get 3 shots or 2 shots with Rumpan, 2 with Rumpan and 1 with candy.
Please come and visit us!
On the other hand, on July 1, there will be an open radio show called Amefura Night on Amefura Flash!
The first-come, first-served lottery period is over, but the first-come, first-served general public tickets will be available from June 26th, so please come and visit us!
Please come and see us!
Next, on July 4, I will be performing as a soloist at the Acoustic Night Fantasy.
Tickets are on sale until 6:00 p.m. on July 3.
I'm going to decide the set and the songs I'm going to play, so please come and see me. I've been singing and trying to decide which songs I'm going to play today.
I'm still a little bit torn, but I'm looking forward to it.
You don't answer to one or two or three requests. No Western music.
Not this time.
I know, it's hard.
Just say, "Pumpernickel." But actually, he's got one Yuzu song in mind.
I'll find it and send it to you.
I'll look for it, too.
Well, this might be a member's express, but you can look forward to it.
What will it be? Perfume, perfume, perfume. I'm going dancing.
Come on, come dance Yuzu will dance He made a puddle
You know, the other night at karaoke, Yuzu danced with Perfume
Hana sang. That collaboration.
Yuzu's dancing was the main attraction, but Hana's singing became the main attraction
Yeah, I was in a hurry to change the keynote while Hana was singing.
I was in such a hurry to change the keynote so much while the flowers were singing, that the flowers became the main focus.
I want the dancing to be the main thing this time. That's not what I meant, I changed it.
I'm getting off track now.
Yes, we are going to perform at a festival called "Spark 2023 in Yamanakako" on July 15th!
Tickets are on sale now, and the second round is over.
The second round is over, but more details will be coming soon, so please wait for them.
Please wait for the details. I'm looking forward to it.
Yes, and...
And which one is it?
We'll be performing at Lucky Fest on July 17th.
Yay!
Yes, we'll be the top performer on the Hills Stage at 11:00 a.m.
Amefurashi is selling kickets.
The place is Hitachi-Keihin Park in Ibaraki Prefecture.
We'll be the top performer, so we'll do our best to get the crowd fired up!
Please come and join us!
Please come and visit us!
And the next day, July 18.
I, Juana, will be performing in a big comedy competition in Musashino.
Oh, my gosh!
Yes, in the presence of comedians.
It's tough.
I'm going to do my best as a one-person idol.
Just one person!
By all means, everyone, please come practice your laugh!
Hanane-san, no matter how you slip up, I want you to laugh at Hanane-san.
That's right. No matter how unfunny it is, please laugh hysterically.
Please do.
Kickets are on sale.
Yes, please
Please.
Chloe, I forgot.
That's next.
I'll go for this one.
Yes, and this is it.
From July 27th to July 31st, I'll be performing at a festival in Taiwan called "Manga Expo".
Yay!
This is a festival in Taiwan.
It's a big festival that is expected to attract more than 600,000 people.
We are really looking forward to it.
We are also going on a fan tour.
Let's go with them and have a fun summer and festival!
Let's have a fun summer and enjoy the festival!
We had a lot of delicious food.
I didn't make it to the music video shoot.
I recommend the green onion buns!
It was delicious. Please try it.
Please do.
Can I talk to you?
Did you see the food at the Lucky Fest Yuzu stall?
I did! It's great!
It's super good.
I'm the last one to see it, and don't you want to see it in season?
I want to see it, and there were enough food stalls to eat the whole time.
Petals made me cry
I laughed at you.
While eating yakisoba
It's the season to get up in the air
Who can get soft?
Who? Who? Who?
Who's that? Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh?Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh? What's that?
It's been there the whole time.
I'll have some more later.
I'm looking forward to it.
There are so many places to eat. It's summer, so you can eat all kinds of delicious food.
There are lots of food stalls.
I'm looking forward to it.
And speaking of food...
We're connected.
We're connected now!
Good luck.
First up...
Friday, June 23rd at 7:00 p.m.
I and Hana will be appearing on Kukupad Live!
This time, we'll be the Yuzu-Hana pair
Now that Hana is here, you can rest assured
I want someone to fail each of us.
Leave it to me this time
I'll fail!
We'll make a big mistake together.
And we'll leave the melon in good shape.
I want to fail, don't you?
I can't fail.
It's easy... because you do it in a way that I can't explain.
I want to fail.
I'm going to lose my elegeler.
I'm gonna lose it.
I've never done this before, and you might say you're the first person to fail.
You might want that assurance.
I do.
I'd like to invite you to come and see the moment of the scorching.
You can watch it for free on Kookpad Amplifier.
We have a premier press conference.
We'll have all kinds of scores and stuff.
I'd be happy if you could all watch it.
Please do.
And then...
Monday, June 25th, 9:30 in the morning.
Tokyo FM Ota-san Presents
The 5th Good Morning WISH
Aine Atties will appear on
It's an elegiac radio show, but it's going to start in the morning.
He's very kind.
He did some research on us before he came on the show.
And we talked about TikTok and so on.
We talked a lot about TikTok and other things.
I'd like you to listen to it if you like.
He was so kind.
It was great.
It was amazing.
I felt like I was looking in the mirror of a celebrity.
I'm looking forward to it.
It was a lot of fun.
I'm sure you'll all find it interesting.
I'd be happy if you could listen to it.
Thank you very much.
And you know what?
Today at 10:00 p.m.
Yami Hi Dash's official YouTube page will be open!
The dance practice of the drama will be released!
The drama is getting a lot of attention on TikTok.
We didn't have a lot of live footage of the drama, so...
I think people wanted to get some material! I think that's why we made this dance practice.
So we made a dance practice!
And we put on some cute outfits.
We also got a really good camera for it.
It was great to see them dancing so energetically!
Look at that!
We don't post a lot of drama on TikTok.
You all have your favorite cameras.
But we haven't posted much on TikTok.
So you can look at it and see how it's done.
I think it would be great if you could see the whole picture of what we're like.
Please do.
And this week on the 24th
Lilliway at Raraport Toyosu, starting at 12:00!
Yay!
It was free!
This is the final of the Reliway.
There's only one more time.
It's only from 12:00pm!
So everyone is definitely working hard to get 500 people to show up.
But after the scoring session is over, we're going to have an encore live show.
There's going to be another live show.
I heard there's going to be an encore live performance, so...
I just can't make it in time for 12:00.
But if you think you can make it just for the encore live...
I'd love it if you could come to the encore live show, even if it's just for the encore.
I'd be happy if you could come and see us.
Please do!
I can't tell you what the score will be for this one day only.
I can't tell you.
I think it's something special.
There's something that you can't do without coming here on this day.
It's free of charge, so I hope everyone will come and enjoy the show.
For us, the count is
the number of people at the show.
If you come from the encore show, it might not count.
That's right.
From 12:00.
We'd love it if you could come.I'd be happy if you could come.
Of course, I'd be happy just to do an encore live performance.
But I'd like to make it to 500 people
And we'd like to do the same for the July 9th show.
We're on a good wave.
We're achieving our goals one by one.
Hey.
I want to do my best.
If you want, please invite your friends and come a lot!
I'm counting on you!
Okay, that's it.
We're heading to the last release event.
We'll do our best to reach 500 people.
I'll do my best to get 500 people.
But...
Sorry.
You know...
I wonder if 500 people will show up.
That's right.
I guess we'll just have to rely on this corner.
Depend on it?
But first, Mike said we don't have any spacha.
No spacha?
Mr. Rat One has asked us to take the next step.
He wants us all to run through the summer together.
Thank you very much.
Shall we go to this corner?
Let's do it.
I'm going to rely on this corner.
That's right.
Let's go.
Whatever.
I hear more and more people are looking for girlfriends.
I'd love to see you use your good looks to sub...
Yeah, whatever.
I hear she's getting more and more attractive, too.
What?
I'd like you to see her in person.
In person.
Raw.
It's no exaggeration to say that the word "buzz" now refers to her!
If we can't reach the goal of 600 IRIBEEDOWINS.
It's not an exaggeration to say that it's his fault if we don't reach 600 people.
There is a person who needs to be told about the charm of this person.
No, I don't mind...
I'd like to start the third installment of this series that will help you get to know us a little better.
Okay.
May I begin? Go ahead.
You've already done it.
I'm so embarrassed.
Nice to meet you, Ira!
Wow!
I'm so happy to meet you.
Is that me?
That's not me?
Ira?
Me?
Ira, it's me.
Isla?
I'm sorry, it's nothing.
Oh, thank God.
Ira.
I'm going to say this is the third and final
This is the third and final installment of this series.
The last one?
Yes, ma'am.
Ira.
Ira, thank you very much.
Thank you very much. I'm Ira.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Last? This one.
Because July 3rd is sold out.
I already said that before the LaLaPorte show, because after that...
We don't do this. We don't do this.
But since Laraporte is over and the tickets are sold out, what's the point?
I'm always the last one to do it, and I don't do it.
But that doesn't mean we have to do it.
It's not that there's no point in doing it.
Let me do it.
Well, well, well... you're a shining star, so you don't have to do it.
You're the talk of the town in China.
You don't say that. You don't say that in China.
It's a festival in Japan.
I'll say "festival.
So, nice to meet you, let's play Ira!
Yay!
Are you okay today?
I've got to get into it.
Yes, sir.
Yes, this is...
Not only for those who have recently come to know me.
As well as those who have been supporting us for a long time.
To let you know more about us...
This is an in-depth project featuring each and every member of AmeFlash.
This is an in-depth look at each and every one of our members.
Yes, sir.Yes, sir.
This time it's Ira.
Ira.
Nice to meet you.
Let's do this.
Can I start by introducing myself?
You should write it down.
I didn't have to.
I didn't.
No, I didn't.
I'm Ira.
No music.
No, no music.
Did you throw it away? Where did you dump it?
Where's the music?
We have our own introductions.
I'm sure of it.
No, some might think it's Ira.
Where did you dump it? The music.
Where did you dump it?
I dumped him in a previous life.
Uh, yeah.
And... and... and...
Did you fail?
Yes, I did.
Uh...
I'm 20 years old.
I love dancing, singing and music.
I like ramen, white rice, shaved ice, ice cream and green tea.
I hate natto and eggplant.
Stop eating natto in front of me!
I love eggplant too.
Natto and eggplant
You might think I'm hard to talk to.
I'm probably the dumbest person you'll ever meet.
Easy to talk to
No, it's hard to talk to him.
On the contrary
On the contrary.
I can't get along with him.
I can't communicate in Japanese.
I can't understand what they're saying when I talk to them.
I love to have fun.
It's fun, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
I'm usually at home on my days off.
But when he wants to go out, he's the kind of person you want to go out with.
She likes the ocean.
What are you doing? What are you doing?
Twilight by the sea.
Yo! Twilight girl!
Romantic.
You went to all that trouble with the representative.
Shoujo manga.
I'm really sorry.
No, no, no.
We're going on a road trip.
You're so outdoorsy.
She's pretty active.
Twilight at the beach.
Here we go.
Ananihoro
They come on holidays, don't they?
What were we doing on our lunch break at school?
Stop it, stop it, stop it
I was playing guitar by myself.
I didn't play for fun.
I was playing in the garden. I was playing the guitar all the way to Garden Hillow.
I played guitar all the way to Garden Hollow.
Practicing for work.
Was anyone listening to you?
Just me.
I didn't have any friends.
At high school.
Are you sure you want to tell them?
It's public.
I thought it was bad information.
I'm glad.
Miyu told you that, didn't she?
No, no, no. This isn't a project to mess with.
It's not a project for me to mess with, either.
That's not what I meant.
I'm glad.
What was it?
The ocean.
There's a restaurant I really like in front of Yugahama.
I like to eat there and then go back to the beach.
Can I say "Yugahama"?
It's okay.
I'll wait for you at Yugahama Beach every day.
That's good.
That's good, too.
So...
I don't know if I like to be too active.
I guess I prefer to stay still.
But... when it comes to playing, I have the image of super-playing.But you know, when it comes to playing, I'm under the impression that I'm super-playful.
It's 0 or 100.
I have an image of being active.
So when I'm out and about, I play a lot.
Like, "I'm going to this restaurant today with my family.
I have the image of going out to eat in all kinds of places.
I love to eat, so I go to all-you-can-eat restaurants.
I fill my stomach.
Filling up.
Fill my belly.
Basically, I'm a lazy person.
I'm a person who can't move until I'm ready to do something, because it's really 0 or 100.
That's all of us.
That's all.
Introduce yourself.
Thank you very much.
That's all.
Well, I guess that's it then.
What?
Is everything okay?
Are we done?
You know what I'm talking about.
No, some of you don't.
Maybe you don't know.
So where do you want to go from here?
Well, you know...
We all do that, don't we?
First Impressions Quiz
Okay, let's do it.
Let's do a first impression quiz.
I'll have everyone write down their first impression of me, and I'll guess it.
Oh, go for it.
But I haven't made any first impressions lately.
You know, people who've told me about you...
I know you're like this, but...
But my first impression of you and your current impression of me are quite different.
I have no idea.
I don't even remember who I used to be.
Is that a true first impression?
Holy shit!
You're scaring me.
First impressions when you remember.
My first impression of you when I remember you.
But I think I know Yuzu.
Hey, maybe Yuzu will understand.
Maybe Yuzu will understand.
That's scary.
But I don't remember my impression either.
How old were you then?
Fourth, fifth and sixth grade.
Sixth or fifth grade?
Fourth grade, fifth grade, sixth grade.
Fourth grade?
I was in sixth grade.
Oh, so grade five.
Fifth grade, while we're at it.
Fifth grade. I don't remember at all.
I wonder if it's okay. I'm sure it's different from the image you have now.
I can definitely recognize Yuzu.
I don't know you two.
I don't recognize you two.
But I think you and Ira were pretty close.
No, I...
We were just hooking up.
I didn't think so.
I mean, you were really close with the other girl, right?
Yeah.
And I wanted to be a part of it, so I kept following her around.
Is that right?
I think I remember that.
I probably shouldn't have told you.
Try it once.
It'll be fine.
I absolutely hate it.
Absolutely not.
Let's try that one time.
I really don't get your impression of Moeka.
I don't.
I don't know.
I don't know what it is.
Try it one more time, okay? May I? Ready? Okay. Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
Oh, my God, it fit. Oh, my God.
It fit. I thought the form was a little different.
The form is something different.
Write down the right answer. Write down the wrong one here.
Just write down why you wrote it once.
No.
Okay, so you've written for four people now.
There's something different about the form.
I'm guessing one at a time.
Something's different.
May I?
I know Yuzu.
I'll start with the yuzu.
You're going to guess first?
Okay.
I'll put them all out.
This one. Flowers are simply black.This way. Flowers are simply black.
My shoulders were black.
She got sunburnt.
You have long hair.
I don't know.
Yuzu is scary.
I think that's what people thought.
I'm guessing this is Yuzu.
I didn't recognize Moeka at all.
I don't get Hana either.
Yuzu first?
This way.
I'm scared.
I've been doing this a long time.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
The first song of our 3D Junior...
Fragile Stars.
At that time...
When we were doing the choreography
Aira made a tempo mistake
and they did the wrong choreography.
In my opinion
I thought maybe she didn't notice.
I just wanted to tell her that it was different
I thought it would be better to tell her that it's different
I thought it would be better to tell her that it's different.
I thought it would be better to tell her that it's different, not from a superior position.
At the time, it was just an "ah-ha" kind of thing.
But Yuzu made a mistake.
I had to change the tempo once.
Yuzu told me that I was wrong.
I was really impressed.
He's so scary.
He's mounted me, so I'm going to get him back.
Yeah.
He wasn't a very nice guy, right?
I was alone.
I wasn't alone.
I was a little chubby.
I had a lot of meat on me.
It was too much.
You know, at the time.
I was like a scary guy with dark skin.
He had dark skin. He looked like a Yankee.
Maybe I had Yankee blood in me.
I was in the fifth grade.
I was rebellious.
You were super rebellious, weren't you?
I was so rebellious.
I didn't know anyone else had that much rebellion.
We were so rebellious.
They were so prickly.
I thought everyone was my enemy.
Back then.
And then came the period when I loved Aira.
And then came the period of black history when he loved her.
She asked me out for Christmas.
Before that...
I was scared.
Why did you start liking her?
I liked her face.
I just liked her face.
I wanted to play with her.
I think it was winter at that time.
I told him I wanted to have fun, and he said he'd play with me for Christmas.
I was happy, so we started playing and I started liking him.
But what was it?
When he came on Christmas Day...
He was an ogre.
He came in clothes.
And you came in a really hideous outfit.
And then he started saying, "I want to go clothes shopping.
He started saying, "I want to go clothes shopping.
I said, "What did I see?
A wolf.
I came in here in my hideous wolf clothes.
I came in here in my hideous clothes.
I said I wanted to see it.
on Takeshita-dori.
neither of the clothes are different from the other
Wiggo at the end of the street and the end of the street
I keep coming back to Wigo
She says, "This is so cute.
The same skirt in both stores every time
It doesn't matter which one you go to.
You could have just gone to one or the other.
I thought it was different.
That's the impression I got.
It's just an impression.
Now that I'm here...
But you want to grow up.
When I think about it, the clothes.
I've grown up a lot.
Yuzu recently posted on Ayanan's instagram
I love it so much.
Be careful
Be careful what Yuzu says to you
What are they saying to you?
I won't tell you.I won't tell you.
It's so lame.
I'm always in the same pose.
You know what I mean?
You know, showbiz people.
They put their faces all over the place.
I'm sure the clients are happy to see that.
Every time I see Ayanan...
She strikes an imposing pose.
From a yuzu's point of view.
I want to see something that's not cute.
I don't like it.
It's better if she keeps it straight.
In all kinds of poses.
Sitting, standing.
I want you to take pictures of me from different angles.
You're cute.
You got the money for tomorrow morning?
I think I'd like to go slowly.
I have an early start tomorrow.
I hope it's not too early.
Two years.
Maybe in two years.
I'll go myself.
I'll be about 22.
I can afford it.
I'll go gradually until two years from now.
Thank you for saving the money
Thank you, sir.
No?
Which one is closer?
Closer.
Close... close.
Okay, Hana-chan.
Half princess, half yankee.
What do you mean?
I don't get it.
The princess...
Totally rebellious period
Between the rebellious years
It's like she's being selfish.
I never talked to her at all.
I've never spoken to her.
I've taken the liberty of...
I'm leading him on.
I didn't talk to him.
I think you were shy, too.
It's just a look or an image.
It's just an image.
And this half-Japanese yankee...
I thought he was half-Japanese.
When I first met Aida
I thought she was half-Japanese.
Not at all.
Born in Tokyo
I'm totally Japanese
The yankee is all about looks.
You know, you have a blog.
There's a photo of him in a yukata.
That's what I'm talking about.
I'm like a super yankee.
Like a gal.
Back then, you know...
I'd ask my mom to check the pictures.
That's weird.
Your mom was a little bit like that.
That's why she's the way she is.
She's a mom gal.
I'm a huge mom gal.
I'm a former gal.
She's out now.
I think she's out.
She was working then.
That's right.
I see.
It's a little different from the black one, isn't it?
Yes, it was.
You're right.
I was a cootie.
That's what I thought.
I see.
Feet?
You've got the wrong foot.
What? I don't know. It's not the right form.
They're connected.
I don't know.
I'm not used to it.
It's like we've connected the bones.
That's what it looks like.
No?
But I used to hurt my leg a lot.
I used to push off my feet.
You have a hand, too.
No broken bones.
I was a bit of a tomboy.
I'd break my legs and stuff.
I mean, you're supposed to be active, so...
She was a real tomboy.
At this time...
Momokuro-san's backing danceMomokuro's back up dance.
I think everyone was there.
I couldn't make it then.
That's right.
I was at the beach with my mom.
I was at the beach.
You didn't get out.
I didn't.
Everyone's amazing.
Sangalas on.
I'm proud to say it.
I liked it when they were doing it.
Oh, yeah.
I'm so lucky.
You're a proud participant.
How often do you do that?
Broken bones.
Injuries.
You're weak.
I don't get hurt that easily.
I just... I just... I used to trip and fall every day.
He loved to play outside.
Playing tag.
Sliding down a bike slide.
That's dangerous.
What do you mean, down a slide?
The bike slide.
If it were today, we'd be in big trouble.
It was a long time ago.
There's a slide.
It's dangerous.
You could get hurt.
That's what made it so much fun.
We'd play tag on the street.
We'd play tag in a small space.
I miss that.
We'd play tag in the rain.
We'd play tag on rainy days.
No, we don't.
He said he'd see me again.
And that one.
Like crocodile bowsers.
That's really hurtful, isn't it?
On the slide.
The demon was under the slide.
The ogre goes up the slide
limping down the slide
The story of where to get hurt in the meadow
It was a lot of fun.
We also played bicycle tag.
We played bicycle tag.
I love it.
It's dangerous.
You can't do that now.
I do it when I'm little.
Yeah, like that.
I had a more mature image of you.
I didn't realize that.
Maybe it's the image of my parents' house.
She was like, "Wow!
Cheerful.
You're very energetic.
Basically, I'm still fine.
People say I don't have many friends.
I've said that myself.
But basically, I'm fine.
You have a mindset of going out to talk to all kinds of people.
I have a mindset of going out and talking to all kinds of people.
I've been getting a lot of that mindset lately.
Aira has always been friendly.
She's very friendly, isn't she?
On the other hand, girls around the same age
It's hard to talk to them.
It's more like adults.
In this industry, you're often in contact with adults.
It's easier to talk to them
I'm less nervous to talk to them.
That's true.
I've known them since I was a kid.
I only play with certain people.
By the way, I've been talking to a staff member, Riddle Girl.
You already said that.
If you tell them who you want to be friends with...
You don't have any friends your own age.
I don't care if we're not the same age.
Other than Kanako.
Other than Kanako and the girls you're close with.
Besides Kanako and the girls you're close to.
Have you hung out with anyone other than Kanako and her friends?
By the way, Staff Rydell...
I don't know... maybe we've had dinner or something, but we haven't hung out.
Good girls don't know that. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
But Kaya asked me to go to this concert, and I couldn't make it
I'm good friends with her, but she's good friends with a lot of people.
I'm so confused about who I want to be friends with.
What should I do?
Is it okay to say what I want to say? What should I do, what should I do, what should I do, what should I do, what should I do?
Is there one in each group? Oh, yeah, that's a given. I want to be friends with all of them.One in each group? Uh, yeah, that's a given. I want to be friends with everybody.
I'd like to be friends with all of them. Maybe just one or two right now. One or two? Wow, wait a minute. What should I do?
But Honoka-chan, Shiochi's Honoka-chan was at Yuzuki's hair festival the other night.
After all the shows were over, we went to say hello to each other, and you talked to each member one by one, right?
You know, we took pictures with Haru-chan, and then Honoka-chan said, "I'm doing the commercial for the Muji voice clock.
How do you do that? I still didn't understand it at the time.
I didn't understand it yet, so I gave a subtle response like, "Oh, that's it," and she said, "No, you can't do that.
He said he'd been like that since the Miniature Bears, so I wanted to go have dinner with him.
Yuzuki Daikoku, please don't be like this.
Please come to us. We'll be waiting for you.
Because Yuzuki-chan used to be a fan of iron, but now she's a fan of Hello!
Yuzuki-chan keeps calling us!
He still doesn't.
I mean, do you have a LINE? No, I don't.
He wasn't here when we exchanged irons.
I'm the only one who doesn't have Yuzuki's LINE.
You have to go there yourself.
You're right.
Don't let the older students tell you.
That's right.
Who were you on the fence about?
Who were you wondering about?
But...
Tokisen-chan's.
I'm interested in Julia.
I know! I know!
Julia-chan.
I have her number.
That's disgusting!
Why do you have it?
Well, I said I'd trade.
You did? That's awesome.
That's great.
But you didn't say anything.
We talked when we traded.
Julia, you know.
I think she's on everybody's mind.
Isn't that strange?
I'd like to get to know her.
She seems like a really, really nice girl.
And she's really cute when she talks.
But she's funny.
She's funny.
But I don't know...
When I'm around her at Stafford Lance Fest.
It's so weird.
They're so cute.
The air is so strange.
You're loving it right now, aren't you?
Yeah, I do.
Yeah, I'm sure.
I want to go every time.
I'm not talking about the moe feeling.
It's Ai Ra, right?
The oldest is like this.
I was the one who befriended you.
I'm sorry.
I wonder... but I really got along with everyone.
I'm pretty shy.
Even when I get to the best part, it's not the best part.
I'd like to be friends with you.
Please come talk to me.
Idiot.
I'm the one who's going to talk to you.
I can see you talking to her.
He's working hard.
I've been talking to Basho and the others about how hard you've been working.
That's great.
I'd be happy if we could get to know each other a little better.
Riko and Ai-chan...
They talk a lot.
That's great!
I'd like to be friends with younger girls, too.
I'd like to be friends with them.
I want to be friends with the students in STAPLA.
I know, I know.
I want to take them out to dinner someday.
I want to take you out to dinner someday.
I'll do my best.
Hey, isn't that you, Aline?
I'll just tell her she can go ahead and compromise and go to Stapler's.
If there was a student, if you could talk to her afterwards, or dm her, or something, she'd be happy to go to the garden with you.
I'm sure she'd be happy to go to the girl's garden with you... buy anything at all, please!
I don't know what's in store, so I'll go along with you... but I don't know what's in store, so don't worry, it'll be fine.
I don't know what's in store for me, so I'll just go along with you.
I'm afraid you'll fail because I don't know... you're probably not so bad yourself.
Compared to Aida, you're better.
I'm spending 330 yen for an accessory! I'm spending 100 yen, or I'm going up, or I'm not coming back...
You can't afford it?
You're the one who doesn't wear it.
I can't afford it.
I'll do it. That's how I feel.
That's true.
Do you want to thank me or something?
You don't want to do that anymore.
Are you okay?
You made me say that a lot.
Isn't everyone always like this?
Three things.
I've only said one.I've only said one thing.
Not that one.
Was there that one item?
That's about all I had to say the first time.
I want to hear it.
Who?
Who do you want?
It's 9:00.
Actually, I'd like to thank 00 or Ai.
Thank you for what? It's going to be a very long walk.
Which one is it?
Thank you for everything.
Thank you so much.
I couldn't have done it without you guys.
So you're actually okay with 00?
I'm actually really grateful.
I'm doing it like this.
I'm super grateful.
I would never have done that.
I'm not.
It's good.
I guess everything is good in a good place.
Tell me you don't need the Souk.
We don't have time for the Souk.
We have another corner.
Tell me.
Yuzu doesn't say much as a representative.
I don't understand.
I said something really nice to Yuzu, didn't I?
I'm sure I did.
Oh, no.
I said something nice to Mayaka, too.
You were too late.
Can't we make Jangachi out of it at least a hundred percent?
Punishment game.
It's not about who loses.
Whoever wins.
One representative.
First one goes "goo", then "jankenpoku".
I said the worst.
Goo, rock, paper, scissors.
That's good.
I wanted to say it.
I've changed to the next door neighbor.
This is the feeling.
This is how I feel.
Thank you.
I want to thank you.
I want to be thankful.
But you don't. At this point.
Thank you.
Thank you for Ilan.
He's not coming out.
Ilan.
You know, you might want to keep an eye on the face and eyes, the winning side.
Tilt it?
All the time,
When I suddenly said I was going to stay at Ilan's,
He said, "Sure.
There?
You said yes.
I couldn't do that. My house is messy.
You said it's too much of a hassle today.
But Ilan said, "Sure, go ahead. He said, "Come over.
He invites me to come over.
I mean, you know, when I was at Ayan's house,
When I'm being attacked, Aylan is always there to help me out,
You know, he would help me out.
You know, something,
That kind of thing,
I'm so happy to see you... after all these years,
You know, after being together for so many years,
I'm very happy to know that you care about me so much after being with me for so many years,
Thank you very much.
I can't do it, even 500 people would be good.
Even 500 people won't come, not like this.
I'm losing face.
Go home, all of you.
There's too little content. There's too little content.
It's a lie.
Well, well, well... I just want to say thank you for everything.
Don't summarize. Really. Don't summarize.
In the good place. The big one.
In a good place. In the good place.
It's impossible.
Well, you know, they forgive me for anything, even if I mess with this part,
Because of what they say, you know,
I can't do it,
That's right. It's only because they let me slip, you know.
Well, in the right place.
In the right place.
If I say it in the right place, it's over.
I really don't have one. I'm sorry.
With all my heart.
I shouldn't have said that. I said something nice last week.
Yes, I did. Did you fall in love with me?
Yes. I love you too.
I love you.
That's all. Nice to meet you, I'm Aira.That's all, nice to meet you Aira.
Thank you very much.
Thank you. Thank you.
Well, this week, there is one more corner that I really want to do.
That's okay. Let's just do it all at random.
Hey. This is an important corner. Let's go.
Okay, here we go. One More Time, One More Time.
Yes, the music video of "One More Time" is now available on YouTube,
I'd like to talk a lot about episodes from the filming, including some of my favorite scenes and behind-the-scenes stories,
I'd like to talk a lot about it.
Of course, you all have seen One More Time, haven't you?
I did.
Have you seen it? Of course you did, didn't you?
Yes, of course. Whenever a music video is released, we always talk about how much we like this or that scene.
Is there?
I'm so happy. 50,000 views and soon to be 60,000.
That's fast.
That's amazing.
That's too fast.
That's fast.
I'm so happy. Thank you, everyone.
I've been watching this for quite a while.
I've been watching this music video.
I've been watching Blow Your Mind for a long time, but I think I'm watching it more than that.
I've seen the expressions on each member's face,
I think I'm watching it even more than "Blow Your Mind",
There are some cute scenes,
Emo scenes.
They're all wearing their own clothes, right?
Yes, all of them.
It's really my own clothes.
I'm Shauner.
I thought I should have worn something prettier.
I wore a black dress.
Yes, can I tell you the number of minutes I like Yuko?
This is Kojima-san at 2 minutes and 41 seconds.
At this time, Yuzu and Hana usually do a lot of TikTok together in their daily lives these days.
Yuzu tends to give TikToks from his boyfriend's point of view,
Yuzu tends to give TikToks from his boyfriend's point of view, and Hana tends to give TikToks from her girlfriend's point of view,
When the two of them are fighting over each other,
I was doing some cool boyfriend-like poses,
I got another shot of them.
Then I was filmed once more doing a cool, awkward, boyfriend-like pose while they were fighting,
I'm sitting on a chair at the airport doing it,
And then Hana-chan is sitting in a chair at the airport doing her "yay" thing, and it's so funny,
Super lame.
Super dorky guy.
They use that.
There were a lot of them.
Yes, there were.
But this is something that we always do in our daily life.
It's nice to have that kind of American Hula in there.
That's good, isn't it?
The everyday life inside.
One of the flowers is used in the spread of the flowers.
I know, it's there.
I know, right?
You know, the jokey part.
A jokey part.
But it's like a candy floss.
It's amazing.
I like that.
I was the cameraman for the airports and stuff, so I was really happy to see my shots used in the music video,
I was really happy to see my shots used in the music videos,
I really liked all of them,
I liked all of them very much, but sometimes other members took pictures of me,
Sometimes the other members would take pictures of me, but it would be 2 minutes 57 seconds or 8 seconds long,
Yuzu and Masai holding hands was taken from behind,
The audience liked that part.
Yes, that's great.
That was great.
I was more interested in you guys than in me holding hands.
You two.
But I feel like Yuzu is holding hands with everyone.
Like, "I'm not holding your hands.
That's how I say it.
I often see Yuzu connecting with Aira.
I've never held hands with Yuzu.
I've never held hands with Aiara.
So they're arm-wrestling.
It feels like they're attached to each other.
I think Moeka prefers hands.
Yay!
I don't know what it is.
Yuzu is sweet on Moeka.
Why is she so cute? I want to marry her.
I've been saying that for a long time.
Yay!
I want to get married right now. Can I write the registration?
Marriage registration.
I'm doing everything.
That's great.
Like, "Let's go to Momotama.
Yuzuko Moe.
They're going to make me do everything.
I'll do everything.
I don't know why Moe is so cute.
They used her for all kinds of things.
You know how you can look at a map when you're on a plane?You know that map-like thing you can see when you are on the plane?
I thought that scene was stylish, so I filmed it,
I thought it would never be used, but it was in there.
I'm sure I'll be able to use it.
To Matsuyama Airport.
It's like a map. Where are we now?
I was so happy to see that it was used.
I was so happy to see that they used that map.
I thought it was nice.
I had taken a lot of pictures.
Yuzu also had a scene where the plane goes up like this.
Yuzu shot that.
Aren't you happy?
I used to use the same place.
Everyone looked alike, but Yuzu really wanted me to use that part.
That's what he was aiming for.
He was shooting for it.
He didn't use it.
Glad. Glad.
Guys, you two.
Hana is the pigeon at 2:13.
Pigeons? Pigeons are so cute! I love pigeons like that!
So cute! This is the scene that surprised me the most when I saw this movie. I was so surprised.
The one where they all ate together? It's the pigeon we all ate together, right?
No, it's not! No, we didn't eat them!
The pigeon comes after the flowers, but the pigeon scene is surprisingly long. Indeed.
They are so cute! He's doing the "pop-pop" thing.
I can do that with just the flowers.
It's super cute. I really want you to see it, here.
My personal favorite part is about 15 seconds in, Hana was filming Moeka.
It's cute. The part of Hana's bar reading.
Cute! So cute!
Cut it off, super low. The first part where the idol says to everyone.
Did you eat that yesterday?
Isn't it really dry? Like, really cold.
It's also disgusting. It's disgusting.
I was saying it in a normal tone, in my opinion. Because of his low voice.
Hana, I ate this yesterday, but I don't want it.
I didn't mean it like that at all.
It's nice, isn't it?
It's a little bit of the real thing coming out, but it's also ennuiemo, and it's cute.
It shows a little bit of our cute side, rather than our usual, hard-edged, determined side,
It was like a different kind of film camera.
I don't know what time we woke up. It was very early in the morning.
Two o'clock.
2:00 in the morning.
Start of makeup.
This is probably the ocean scene, like 4:00 in the morning.
Yeah, like 4:00 in the morning.
I don't know what time it is.
Good morning? Good night.
Good morning.
I had to go to the airport this morning and come back. To Japan.
Right. Yes, yes. Yes, yes.
Memories. Various.
It's natural. Really.
Even when I show them to you, it's just the image of everyone as they are normally.
Really?
I'm happy.
It's beautiful.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
There is a behind-the-scenes story. There is a scene where we are playing in the ocean like this.
Everyone was playing with their feet up in the air as if they were wading in the water,
Our Mr. Kojima tried to pretend to do the same thing to Mayaka.
Then he really kicked her. Sand was sticking to her white one-piece dress,
Suruga-san looked angry or depressed,
She said, "It's okay.
There was nothing I could do, and I couldn't do it anymore.
There's no point in getting angry and feeling depressed and helpless.
It's totally fine.
The staff felt that atmosphere, too, and said, oh, let's go again.
Zokin, zokin.
Everyone was so excited that they were playing musical notes.
That's for sure.
Yuzu, you were wearing breast clothes, so I didn't go near there at all.
She said, "Oh, I'm going to take it off. When everyone was playing, I thought for sure Ai would do something to the flowers.
I thought they would get dirty.
I was sure they would get water or seaweed or something in there. That's how boys are. Flowers.
I wonder if it's a heavenly thing.
I'm definitely looking forward to it. Oh, he said he's going to take it, take it, take it.
Oh, it was soaking wet.
It was soaking wet. But you got it, sand.
You're mad at me.
It's a memory.
He wants me to pay for the dry cleaning.
Wake me up for the cleaning.
I'm not going to give it to you.
I think we might have the same hair when we get back.
Oh, I'm the same.
Do you want to return it again?
I put it together. It was shaggy from the ocean.
And normal,
I mean, you were on a tight schedule, and then you came home,
I mean, you know, you're on a tight schedule, and you've got a YouTube shoot right after you get back home.
So you usually sleep on airplanes.
What? Maybe I didn't sleep.
I didn't sleep much.
No one slept.
Yuzu.
I only slept a little.
No, it's Yuzu. As soon as I went to bed, I turned into that thing.No, it was Yuzu. As soon as we went to bed, it turned into that, right?
That's right.
I was like, "Wow.
Go back to sleep,
Yuzu,
Panic.
Yuzu, I got a really weird disease.
It was something like that.
What was it?
I fell asleep for about five minutes.
And when I woke up,
I don't know, something, right after I woke up,
I got sick.
Yuzu, yes, I was awake and everyone was sleeping,
On the plane, right?
Yes, I was.
And my nose was kind of fuzzy, and then Yuzu,
Yuzu started to say, "Ha-ha-ha!
I thought, "What, what, what happened all of a sudden? I thought, "What's going on?
I thought he was joking about his nose, too,
I was laughing a little bit,
Hey, what are you doing?
What do you mean? What are you doing? Like, "What are you doing?
I said,
He said, "My ears hurt, my ears hurt.
It got really bad.
What's wrong? He said, "What's wrong?
I woke up because of the commotion.
I cried so hard.
I was like, "Ha-ha!
It was amazing. Yuzu was already there,
Yes, she was cowering,
When I woke up and looked to the side, I saw Yuzu,
I woke up and looked to the side.
I was like, "Nee" in my head.
Yuzu is going to disappear like this.
What should I do?
This is where I say goodbye to everyone.
So, at first, I really thought it was a joke.
But then I started to cry.
Yes, I cried really hard.
So I thought, "Oh no,
You know how the moment you wake up, the air pressure makes your ears curl?
I think I did that the moment I woke up.
I was reflecting on what I had done.
I started crying, so I covered myself with the futon.
I covered myself with the futon and started to woo-woo-woo-woo.
Yes, I'm doing it,
I definitely want to cry.
Big cry.
The other one is crying a lot.
Yuzu, as expected of Aira,
What's the big deal? Do you want some water?
I said, "I'll give you some water.
You were crying?
I was crying so hard.
I didn't know.
I really don't know if I should make it relative. I really wasn't sure.
What do you mean "relative"?
Finally, we were all like, "Oh my God, we can't go to the candy festival after this,
I said, "I can't go to the Ame-chare after this,
Aira said, "Let's stop, let's go home.
I was already worried,
But then there was the candy festival, and after that..,
It was like, "I can't do this.
I can't do this.
This is Yuzu's fault,
I'm not lying, it's true.
That's when I was in the middle of it,
I was in a lot of unexplainable pain.
We both hurt.
I hurt here and I hurt there.
Ever since we were in Taiwan, I had a constant pain in the back right side of my body.
Ika slept like a bomb in the middle of all that.
Nothing happened.
I was like, "What should I do, what should I do?
Yuzu-san, you won, right?
I couldn't make sense of it at all.
I couldn't believe it was after crying,
We were all like, "Foo!
We went around quickly.
I think there was, but I wish they'd try one more time.
I think it was after I cried.
We didn't film the scene where she cried.
I don't have any.
We'll talk again next week.
Yes, we will.
Four or five minutes have already passed.
It's time to say good-bye for the last time,
I just want to do the Moe Moe magic.
Wait a minute.
It's okay.
I think your feet are fine.
I'm sorry, I'm shivering right now.
I was cold for a second.
I didn't hear you say that about Suicune.
It was a real chill.
So, nose already?
Not today.
No, I can't.It's no good.
My body says I'm at my limit.
It's no good. Suicune is super cute this time.
Good night.
Super cute. This time, it's not good.
Suicune recently,
In the kitchen.
rice container in the kitchen.
And that's where Suicune
to eat there.
But we eat at home.
eat at home.
So we eat in the living room.
Sukikun eats separately.
We eat in the living room.
So, I don't know.
Sukikun eats at that timing,
Sukikun always eats at the place where he eats.
He always crunch his food.
And when Hana goes to see what's going on
And then she starts eating.
And when I went back to the sofa, he started crunching his food again.
And when I went back to the sofa, he started crunching the rice again.
And when Hannah goes to him, he starts eating.
It's so cute.
He wants her to eat with him. I want you to watch.
Watching them eat.
But I thought if I did that every time, there would be no end to it.
Hannah ignored it.
Then, she followed the food box
to her own place.
to where everyone else was eating.
She chased after them.
And took pictures of her eating.
Cute.
I wonder if the footage will beat the current episode.
That's what I'm going to do.
They're smart, too.
They can understand human language and stuff.
Cute.
Oh, no.
What?
That was fast.
Let me see.
I can't see it right now.
The part where you're bringing it, that's not what I saw.
I saw you bring it, because I thought you brought it,
Oh, I thought it was cute, so I took it.
But when I looked at it now, I saw that he was just eating.
That's why I asked him to make an episode.
No! No!
I had only brought the food box.
I touched it without thinking it was a bad thing.
It's not bad.
I was just thinking about this episode in a normal way,
I probably just touched on it.
No!
So, I brought the food myself and kept eating it there.
While looking at me.
That's not what I meant.
He wanted to bring the story to the footage he shot.
That's not true! It's true!
He kept saying, "What's the point of this?
We have that footage, too.
I'll be asking for it every day.
I want you to do Morimori Suikun or something this week too.
Moe Moe Magic Corner.
Yes, let's go.
That's all for this week, too, Morimori Suikun.
I'm going to go.
Well, it's time to say goodbye to this week.
I hope everyone will do their best for the week ahead,
Moeko will give you a spell to get you through the week, and Moe Moe Magic will be here to help you out.
On June 24th, Berryz will be having their finals.
We are aiming for 500 people to agree, so be sure to want to come to Toyosu.
Good luck.
Please come? If you come to the benefit event, Moeiko?
If you come to the benefit, what will Moeiko do for you?
Give him a bang?
I'll bang you.
I'd like that.
All right.
It's like this.
I really don't want to be in the same group.
I hate it.
Then, if you say moe moe zukkun, moe bakkun, I'll do it.
Please say it.
Are you the manager?
That's fine.
This is the oldest member of our group.
He is our biggest fan.
I'm worried about his future.
Hey.
There is a video of Suicune calling and eating.
It's fine.
There won't be a next time, so it's normal.
I'm going to say that much and put it out.
Moshagomosha.
When it's crunchy and the flower is weak, I'll go take a video.
Hahaha.HAYAYAYAYAYAYAY.
Thank you for watching.
Isn't that Mimio?
I'm looking at Mimio's face.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
You're such a jerk.
Why are you eating at my invitation?
So, Suikun...
I found evidence that you eat when you're called.
There was only a little bit of rice left.
Hey...
That's enough, Hana.
You don't have to work so hard.
Let's end this corner.
If you're having a hard time, you should just say so.
It's a giraffe.
Eat it.
I think it's gone.
Oh, spacha spacha.
Suicune. I think there's something in there.
Spacha Spacha's gonna use it.
It's true.
But maybe it's not the same thing.
Maybe it's not.
Well, whatever. It's a match.
Thank you very much, Cathy.
And now, please look forward to next week's moisture.
Mamma Mamma will be back!
Next week, Mamma Mamma will be at home in Styland.
So please look for the sixth generation.
Yes, he's here.
I'd be embarrassed if you introduced Mammal-chan here.
More than Suicune, that's for sure.
Even Suicune is doing his best to stay alive.
I'd like to see something good soon.
I'd like to see something good.
That would be super cool.
It's cute.
Please get me a funny Suicune that's fishing.
Please do.
It's time to say goodbye.
Let's all go together for the last time.
Let's go!
Let's talk ameddle while we're ameddling!
Ame-hura chat for short!
Bye bye!